My name is Philomina Sunday. I am a widow.
I am a mother of nine children.
I have been suffering, begging for food to eat. Nobody will assist me.
I started going to dustbins to pick food to eat.
Even the clothes that I am wearing, I picked them from the dustbin, washed them to wear.
Even for my children, I will pick clothes from the dustbin and wash them for them to wear.
If we don't go to the dustbin early, we will not find food to eat.
When we go there early, we will find food to pick there.
Sometimes when we go there, we will find some foods like yam, corn, bread and groundnut.
We will pick all of those things there.
Things have been very difficult for me.
There was a woman who saw me at the dustbin.
She asked what I was doing at the dustbin with these children, picking food every day.
I said there was nobody to help me.
I have been suffering. If I go to people to give me money, they will disappoint me.
My boyfriend - I was thinking that he was going to help me and my children,
to send them to school. But the man disappointed me. He could not do it.
I told the woman that this is where I get food to eat.
She then asked me if I knew about The SCOAN. I said, "No".
She said she would help me.
I asked her how was she going to help me get to The SCOAN
because I didn't know anybody there.
The woman told me that I should not worry.
There was a day we went to a dustbin.
We were collecting food and cans.
We would sell the cans for 50 naira and use the money to buy food to eat.
The woman then came to me and told me that we should prepare now.
The woman chartered a bus and put us on it.
She said that if I wanted the man of God to really believe that I am suffering,
I should give the man of God this cassette and he should watch it
to see how I am suffering.
The woman gave me the cassette that I should take it to The SCOAN,
that the man of God would help me.
Let us watch the video.
Is that where you live??
Yes, sir.
This is where you sleep?
Yes.
No matter your level in life, you are a solution to a problem.
Where is your husband??
He died in 2004, on the 18th of August.
Where is the senior one?
The senior daughter is here.
She has married?
Yes.
My Name is Abumare Faith.
What my mother is saying is true.
Because of the suffering, I saw a man that said he was going to keep me in his house.
I didn't know the man was suffering. I have two children from him.
He doesn't have any work.
The clothes I am wearing are from the dustbin.
My mum came one day and told us that she had something to tell us.
She said that a woman told her to go to The SCOAN.
I know that as we have come here, our story will turn around.
Whatever we want to do to restore this family, let them be part of our family.
We will counsel them so that these children will not be destroyed.
She has no reason for getting married but because of problems.
That is what she is saying
They have to get accommodation. These children have to go to school.
They will go for deliverance now.
That poverty is not just poverty
but it has become a curse and Jesus can remove this curse.
All over the world. People like this - they are everywhere.
Please find them, help them and restore them.
Don't just pass by and close your eyes.
What can we do? Let us put an end to this.
First, we want to give her 500,000 naira.
They can give them 10 bags of rice.
They will stay in the church until we get them a house.
My Name is Anthonia.
I thank the man of God for what he has done for us.
Since my mother has been suffering, I saw a man that said he liked me.
He made me pregnant.
After I gave birth to my baby, I found out that the man at times has a mental problem.
This June, the mental problem started.
Sometimes he will start behaving strangely outside.
People will start running away.
He used to beat me and my baby. Sometimes he will kick us out.
My mother doesn't have anything.
If I go to her, she doesn't have anything to give me.
She doesn't have any place to keep me and my baby.
Man of God, please help me.
That marriage should be immediately terminated.
It is a wrong marriage, caused by poverty. Your future first before marriage.
Let them face their career and future.
If the Lord says they will marry tomorrow, they can marry tomorrow.
But that marriage should be stopped for now.
What a beautiful baby girl! Look at this one.
What is your name?
Esther.
Wow - look!
Watch your screen.
Look at the face!
Man of God, I have something to tell you.
I am thanking you for removing me from poverty to riches today.
I am thanking you for all the good things you have done for me.
You will live long!
The opposite is the case now. I am to thank you for receiving this gift.
Thank you for receiving this gift.
You will live long!
Thank you.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Philomina Sunday. I am a widow.
I am 42 years old.
I am from Kogi State (Nigeria).
These are my children and grandchildren.
My husband died 5 years ago.
Since then things have been difficult for me.
I have been suffering, begging for food, going to dustbins to pick food to eat with my children.
I thank God today that my case is over.
My husband was a very big man.
When I complained to him that I wanted to start a business,
he asked me what type of business I wanted to start.
I told him that I wanted to sell cows.
He gave me the money to start the business.
We were living fine and rich.
When my husband had an accident and broke his ribs,
I was taking him to different hospitals, spending money.
He then told me that the money is finished.
He said he was going back to his villiage.
We prepared to go to his village.
He sent me to bring a document,
telling me that I should not return on Monday but on Friday.
I asked him why he asked me to return on Friday.
He said it was so that he could prepare our property in the house.
I said okay.
I then went to Asaba.
On Thursday, I called Anthonia's phone number; it wasn't going through.
I was calling her daddy's number but it also not going through.
So, I had to call my husband's cousin.
That was on Friday morning. I was feeling cold all over me.
I could not get myself.
He then told me that my husband had died.
I asked what had killed him.
He said double cross my heart and to start coming,
not to call any of my family to come. I said no;
I had to go and call my parents and my uncle. They followed me to that place.
My Husband died on August 18th, that was on Thursday at 6 o'clock.
They buried him at 12 o'clock, midnight.
They didn't allow me to see the corpse. There were a lot of complaints.
I said, "God, let Your will be done".
When my husband died, there was no money with us.
Since then I have been going to the dustbin to pick food, cans and clothes.
I sold the cans to get money.
To eat once in a day was difficult.
That is why my daughters fell into that situation, to meet a man to help.
They got married and had children.
This is my first daughter and she has three children because of our poverty.
My second daughter Anthonia has a baby girl from a man.
The husband has a mental problem.
The other children are not going to school anymore.
My name is Anthonia Sunday. This is my baby.
I thank God for what He has done in our lives,
for using Prophet T.B. Joshua to bless my family with 500,000 naira and 10 bags of rice.
We are very happy.
Now we no longer need to pick food from the dustbin but eat at the dining table.
God should continue to bless Prophet T.B. Joshua for all that he has done for us.
After giving Mrs Philomena Sunday and her family the sum of 500,000 naira and 10 bags of rice,
Prophet T.B. Joshua sent the Emmanuel TV team to look for and rent an accommodation
that would be suitable for them as they prepare to open a new chapter in their lives.
This is the accommodation they finally chose.
One by one the Emmanuel TV team enter, carrying different pieces of furniture
that would transform this new appartment into a comfortable home for the family.
New furniture, appliances and upholstery are being brought in,
soon to be arranged so that the family can move in.
In comes the new mattress and the frame for the bed.
As a finishing touch, the Emmanuel TV team and Partners purchased two comfortable chairs
and a coffee table to adorn the sitting room.
What an amazing contrast!
A family who was once suffering, living on the streets and eating from dustbins
is now about to move into a safe, clean, pleasant and comfortable environment.
What a transformation!
Glory be to God!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.